Back orders
and you never
called them.
Can you believe this?
There's a dog
in the car.
You can't leave a dog
in a parked car!
Snowboarder, it figures.
Do snowboarders
hate animals?
I bet this guy
didn't leave his weed
in the car.
Okay, we have to do something,
because this is
incredibly dangerous.
Oscar, it's not
that hot out.
A car parked in the sun
is like a toaster oven.
Well, we don't know how long
the driver's been gone,
and it's not
in direct sunlight.
So what, Andy?
You want to just
let him die, you scumbag?
Here, I'm going
to get in my car.
When I start dying,
I will honk
the horn three times.
That means
save the dog.
DWIGHT: Okay,
you know what?
I'm going to give him
something to drink.
Come here, doggy.
(WHISTLING)
Come on.
Dwight,
at least aim it.
There you go.
Here, doggy.
He's not even trying.
Come here,
doggy, come on.
We're losing
cloud cover.
Don't try to get in
on it now, Michael Vick.
Hey, hey, hey.
Vick did his time.
This guy's been gone
long enough. He's lost
his right to a window.
Get back, buddy.
Get back.
Oscar, what are you...
What... No, hey!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
All right.
MEREDITH: Yeah!
JIM: Nice job, Oscar.
And one
for good measure.
(ALL GASPING)
Yeah!
So, who's going
to take the dog?
Why would we
take the dog?
What if he jumps out
the window and runs away?
Jim, he's not
going to start...
(BARKING)
OSCAR: Stay, stay.
Nein. Sitz!
Gut.
Oscar, what do you want to do?
This is kind of your deal.
You want a dog?
There we go,
that should do it.
Yeah, it's good.
It'll work.
JIM: Nice job.
Bye, poochie.
Bye, doggy.
(BARKING)
Bye.
(CAR HORN HONKING)
(BARKING)
(HORN BLARING)
What's that come to?
Like, what did
they each win?
Oh, man, it's gotta
be over $100,000.
Yeah, before taxes.
PHYLLIS: That's still
a lot of money.
The warehouse crew won
the lottery yesterday.
$950,000.
And then they quit.
And no one else
can focus.
This is it.
This is all
on my shoulders.
I'm the one who has to tell
everyone to get back to work.
I'm the one who has
to tell Darryl to hire
a new warehouse crew.
I'm the one who has
to say those things.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Hello?
Justine. (LAUGHING)
Nice surprise.
How you doing, baby?
No, no, no.
I didn't win.
When I got promoted,
I stopped...
What?
Yeah, Glenn won.
You want to call him?
Yeah, you should call him.
Congratulate him.
That would be...
What?
His number is
in your old phone.
Oh, you know what?
I might have it right...
(PHONE BEEPING OFF)
Whoops.
When I worked
in the warehouse, I was
part of that lotto pool.
They won
playing my birthday.
What really interests me
is the group dynamic
of six people
winning the lottery.
This will not
end well, right?
Yeah.
We're looking at,
at least one suicide
and one weird sex thing.
At least.
I don't even know what
I'd do with all that money.
I know what you'd do
with all that money.
"Hey, Pam.
Let's buy expensive
bathrobes and hug."
No, I'd probably
buy a big piece
of land in Maine,
build a house,
work in town.
Somewhere I could
bike to or kayak to.
I'd either bike to my job
at the kayak shop
or I'd kayak to my job
at the bike shop.
And then on the weekends,
would you hacky sack
back to reality and spend time
with your wife and kids?
Whoa, Saucy,
I thought you
liked Maine.
I think we should get
a townhouse in Soho.
Soho's mostly lofts,
but okay.
And then, every morning,
I'd walk out onto my terrace,
and I would breathe in
the inspiration of the city.
You know, and just gather
ideas for my painting.
Oh, God.
And then my
handsome husband...
Which, ideally,
would be me.
Would bring me
a flavored coffee.
Stop. I'm a barista
in your fantasy?
Well, in your fantasy,
we're Stephen King
characters.
I don't know
about Stephen King.
Get a divorce.
I think I would
keep working.
And for my salary,
I guess I would take,
like, $1 a year.
Obviously, I wouldn't
come in till noon.
And I wouldn't do anything
I didn't want to do.
I mean, I'm getting paid
$1 a year, okay?
You can chill.
Are you kidding me?
Guys, if I have to ask you
to get back to work
one more time,
I'm gonna change my tone.
(IN DEEP VOICE)
To down here, like Mr. T.
And this would get
seriously annoying.
I feel sympathy for the jerks
who have to listen
to this all day.
Darryl.
How we doing on
the new warehouse guys?
I don't know.
What... Do we have
new guys?
No.
Are they on
their way over?
I haven't hired anyone.
What? No warehouse guys?
I have an important order
that has to go out by 5:00.
I e-mailed you about it.
I'm not checking
e-mail till lunch.
Four hour work week.
ANDY: This is kind of
time-sensitive.
I got it. I'm doing it.
Andy, this is a seriously
big order. I can't
lose this client.
All right, well,
until we have a new crew,
let's get some volunteers
for warehouse duty.
Who's in?
As long as you guys
don't need me up here.
I think we'll be fine.
No, we don't.
Really? Nobody's going
to help her?
Is chivalry dead?
Are you volunteering?
Of course, I would.
But my hip...
I would kill
to be at 100%.
ANDY: Jim, how about you?
Yeah. I mean,
as the strongest person
in this office,
I guess I should...
Okay, no, no.
That... You are
so not... Oh, God.
(GRUNTS)
False. Andy,
I will volunteer.
Great.
And Kevin.
(SIGHING)
Good old Kevin.
He'll do anything.
Well, guess what?
I will not do
a good job.
Thank you.
Sure.
Wait, wait.
What's this?
Oh, sorry.
I thought it was a
guess-your-baby's-birth-weight
pool.
It says "lotto pool"
right on top.
Yeah, and I said sorry.
Oh, come on.
You really think
I'm going to have
a 14-pound baby?
(KNOCKING)
When did I get so fat?
You look awesome.
I didn't hire anyone,
if that's why you're here.
Where are we
in the process?
I have a file
of applicants here.
I just gotta open it,
look at it,
interview a bunch of guys,
hire some of them.
So I say we're
in the early stages
of the process.
Did you go out celebrating
with the guys last night?
They guys did
invite me out
to celebrate,
but I decided
to just stay home.
Eat a bunch of tacos
in my basement.
You do have
a fantastic basement.
I did.
I did have
a fantastic basement.
Now it smells
like tacos.
You can't air out
a basement.
And taco air is heavy.
It settles
at the lowest point.
Right. Um.
Well, how about we take
a look at some applications?
This guy wrote his
in green ink.
That's pretty cool.
Check it out.
Hey.
There you go.
There he is.
That is not Darryl.
I don't know where Darryl is.
I suspect, probably,
our Darryl is inside
of Fat Darryl.
Okay, 300 boxes
of 20-pound white.
That's 75 boxes per person.
So, that's not so bad.
Negative.
Three hundred boxes for me,
zero for you chumps.
Deal with it.
Nice.
Oh, oh, oh!
Damn.
(SCREAMING)
Yup.
Welcome, everybody.
My name is Andy,
and this is
my other brother, Darryl.
What? No Newhart fans?
Okay.
Darryl, how do we usually
kick these things off?
You mean, what did we do
the last time the warehouse
won the lottery?
Your old crew
Does anyone have experience
shelving, storing,
keeping track...
What do we use?
The Dewey Decimal System?
Wait, wait.
So, all the
old guys quit?
Oh, yeah.
Well...
One of them, Glenn,
is starting one
of those fat camps
where he steals your kid
in the middle of the night.
Madge and a couple
other guys might start
a strip club.
But on a boat.
And Hide is investing
in an energy drink
for Asian homosexuals.
(LAUGHING NERVOUSLY)
Could you guys
give us a minute?
But stay close.
You're all doing great.
Maybe grab a coffee,
or if there's any donuts out,
you can split one.
You know,
they're for everybody,
so people get fussy.
You know what?
Just have a donut.
Do you want to talk about this
not-winning-the-lottery thing?
I don't.
You sure?
'Cause you keep
talking about it, so...
Nope. I'm good.
I'm here.
Let's find some
warehouse workers.
Good, great.
Then, can you say things
that aren't, like, a huge
bummer to everybody?
'Cause the more I talk,
the more they're
going to realize
I don't know
what I'm talking about.
Okay.
We need you, okay?
Okay?
Yeah.
All right.
(GRUNTING)
Ah!
What's the problem?
Grunting is scientifically
proven to add more power.
Ask any female tennis player,
or her husband.
(YELLING)
I didn't feel anything.
ANDY: All right, thank you
for coming back in again.
Now, we're going
to ask you a few questions.
Darryl, you have the floor.
Why do you want
to work here?
I need a job.
It's not a good reason.
Good.
Keeping them honest.
Don't just take
the first job
that comes your way.
'Cause next thing you know,
it's 10 years later,
and you're still there.
You could write
your obituary tomorrow.
It's not going
to change.
Are we scaring
them straight?
I hope so.
Think about
this carefully.
There's better lives
than this one.
I've never been lucky.
And I'm not talking
about the lottery.
I'm talking about
stuff like developing
a soy allergy at 35.
Who gets a soy allergy at 35?
And why is soy in everything?
Nice, right back
where I like you.
Can you make 10 copies
of this for me?
No.
Why not? What
are you doing?
Buying lottery
tickets online.
(CHUCKLING)
Everyone wants to be rich,
but nobody wants
to work for it.
You came in
at 10:30 today, right?
Okay, I'll just
do this myself.
Is everyone licensed?
Like a driver's license?
No, warehouse license.
Masters in
warehouse sciences?
I feel that Darryl has talked
about a license of some kind.
Is this a joke?
No. Not joking.
This is real.
Painfully real,
what is happening
right now.
Okay, I'm not
going to make it.
I'm turning back.
There's gotta be
a better way to do this.
This is literally how
they built the pyramids.
Well, they whipped people,
which was helpful.
But you're right.
We should be able
to find a more efficient way
of moving boxes
than Madge or Hide.
Yeah.
Not that they're
not smart people.
No, no, very smart...
Theirs is
more of a physical
intelligence.
I'd go with that.
Like baboons
or elephants.
Not that, don't...
Guys, when I was a kid,
my sisters used
to butter me up
and slide me
across the linoleum floor
of the kitchen.
It really made
them laugh.
It's a great idea, Kev.
I don't think
it applies here, though.
So, maybe we just...
Yeah, we move stuff
and have fun.
Kevin,
doesn't apply.
Right, my mom...
You need
to drop it, okay?
They hate it.
I like it a lot,
but they hate it,
so drop it.
Does anyone get distracted
easily by bubble wrap?
(LAUGHING)
You'll be dealing with
lots of bubble wrap,
obviously. Um...
How much longer
is this going to take?
Did you hire them?
No, because
they all left.
What do you mean
they left?
I mean, after you bailed,
I got confused,
and frankly,
a little weird.
And the stuff that you said
certainly didn't help.
Then I think you
should fire me.
What are you talking about?
I'm not going to fire you.
Yeah, just put me out
of my misery.
Okay, this is weird.
I don't get the joke.
No? Okay.
I don't want
to be here anymore.
Fire me.
So Darryl says
to me, "Fire me,"
but what he really means is,
"I'm going to say something
really weird, try and figure
out what it means."
So I say, "No,
you're not fired."
But what I really mean is,
"I've no idea
what you're
talking about.
"But I'm going to go ahead
and hire some people
"for the warehouse and hope
that you eventually
start feeling better."
I really hope that's
what he and I mean.
Attention.
Does anyone know anyone who
could work in the warehouse?
We can pay.
Come on, Oscar.
Who's the most jacked guy
in all of Scranton?
Like your wildest
fantasy guy?
Bulk or definition?
Definition.
Bruce Kenward.
He hangs out
at Planet Fitness.
Are those just show muscles,
or is he really strong?
Oh, he's plenty strong.
It used to be Reggie Winters
out at Gold's Gym.
But he moved away.
And then it was between
Bruce and this guy, Dean.
But Dean got fixated
on his calves,
and, uh...
And his triceps
went to hell.
So, I've been thinking,
after we win the lottery,
we take our winnings...
Our fake winnings.
And we move
to the South of France.
See... No, there's plenty
of bicycling for you.
I think that's
where they do
the Tour de France.
It is, yeah.
I mean, I just don't know
why I'm compromising
if it's my fantasy.
Because in my fantasy,
it's Maine, and you love it.
Because I'm never going
to act like that,
even in your fantasy.
Nope, you're doing
a great job of it
in my fantasy right now.
Hey, idiot, what did
Erin want again?
A hot chocolate tea.
Gideon, you are
a PhD candidate
studying America's
diminishing blue-collar
workforce?
North America.
And "diminishing" is a little
reductive, but, sure,
that's the headline version.
Great.
Well, it will bring
a fresh, new perspective
to the warehouse.
FYI, Wednesday through Friday,
I have a pretty full
teaching schedule.
Oh, cool.
We'll figure
that out.
Also, FYI,
I don't technically
have a hearing problem.
But sometimes, when there's
a lot of noises occurring
at the same time,
I'll hear them
as one big jumble.
Again, it's not
that I can't hear.
Because that's false, I can.
Um, I just can't distinguish
between everything
I'm hearing.
Got it. Duly noted.
You,
coolest tank top
I have ever seen.
Where did you get that?
Made it.
So cool.
What a cross section
we have here.
It's what I love
about interviewing.
I get to meet
all these people
I wouldn't ordinarily
meet, or know
or even talk to.
Message in a Bottle,
The Postman...
Kevin Costner.
Kevin Costner, yeah.
So...
I found this grease.
And then I remembered
that you thought
it was a great idea.
You did say
I heard you say it.
So it's not
the dumbest idea.
DWIGHT: It's not the
greatest one...
But the fact remains,
we gotta move these boxes.
And it's clear we're
not going to carry them.
So sadly, it's the best
idea on the table.
Exactly.
KEVIN: Hey, I think we're
ready to get this...
Jim?
Is he okay?
He'll be fine.
Surprise! Your new crew.
Would you just
fire me, man?
Hey, why?
Because you didn't
win the lottery?
How am I supposed
to make you happy?
You want to make
me happy? Huh?
Yeah.
Give me your job.
Haha. What?
I'll do it better
than you.
I earned it,
I deserve it,
I got passed over,
God knows why.
Reasons I cannot
and will not understand.
The job was mine, Andy.
Everyone said it was mine.
Make me manager
or fire me.
I'm not going
to give you my job.
It's my job!
I earned it!
And here's the thing.
You weren't even
next in line.
I asked about you.
I saw your file.
You have a history
of being short
with people,
and you hired Glenn,
your buddy,
to replace you
in the warehouse.
He was under-qualified.
They saw that.
Also, Darryl, FYI,
I already told
this to Andy,
but you should
probably know
I technically don't have
a hearing problem.
It's just when there's
a lot of noises...
Nate. Please.
Thank you.
(INAUDIBLE MUMBLING)
You have no
business education.
You were going to take
classes under Deangelo.
What happened to that?
He died.
He didn't die,
his brain died.
And my brain is still
very much alive.
And I'd be happy
to give you
business classes.
How come you haven't
asked me about it?
What was...
What was the last...
I'm having a...
No part of this has
anything to do with you.
I didn't have time
because of my daughter.
But you had time
for a softball clinic.
And a Mediterranean
cooking class.
Hey, I'm not going to tell you
this stuff if you're going
to throw it back in my face!
Hey, here's the thing.
Jo saw something in you.
She loved you.
She gave you a shot,
and then you
stopped pushing.
She noticed.
Okay.
Okay, what?
Okay, don't fire me.
Okay.
My future's not going
to be determined by seven
little white lotto balls.
It's going to be determined
by two big black balls.
I control my destiny.
I do.
I'll put some
guys on tonight.
The best of your bunch
and my bunch.
I'll tell you now, though,
it's going to be mostly
my bunch.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Okay, good.
All right.
DWIGHT: Are they here?
What is going on?
Oh, hey, guys.
Why is the forklift
in the wall?
ANDY: Why is
the truck empty?
It's not totally empty.
Is that grease
on my floor?
Okay.
I can see why you're angry.
You're coming into this cold.
But believe me,
a lot of thought
went into this.
And did your brains
tell you to ruin these
boxes with grease?
Okay, Darryl.
Listen, and then
you will understand.
The boxes were ruined
during our first
trial testing.
So now, it's cool,
'cause we found
another use for them.
Okay, all right.
That's... Look, all we were
trying to do is we thought
we could come up
with a more efficient
way to do things.
And?
And we did.
I don't know.
Jim, tell them
what it's called.
That's all right.
No, Jim, tell them
what the name is.
Doesn't matter
Señor Loadenstein,
that's stupid.
Señor Loadenstein.
Tell them why
it's called that, Jim.
That's okay, we're good.
No, Jim, tell us why
it's called señor
Loadenstein.
Porque es muy rápido.
DWIGHT: Okay, you know what?
It's been a real busy day.
What do you say
we put all this away?
Let me see it.
It's in beta testing.
Let me see it!
Get the thing, go!
Lube it up.
Kevin, start mopping.
ALL: Uno, dos, tres.
Yeah. I lost my client.
I already won the lottery.
I was born in
the US of A, baby.
And as backup,
I have a Swiss passport.
I would spend
a lot of time
launching my
true crime podcast,
"The Flenderson Files."
Duh-buh-bum.
Flenderson Files.
We came
to an agreement.
We're going to live
in a stunning
pre-war brownstone
at the top of a mountain.
Right, it's city
and country combined.
Just a subway stop away
are the best museums
in the world.
And I can fish right
from the window
of Pam's pottery studio.
We can chat
any time we want.
Just like now.
It's too bad the schools
are terrible, but what are you
going to do about that?
What are you
going to do?